http://www.shults.com/privacy.html

Privacy Statement for Shults Dot Com
Privacy Statement for Shults Dot Com
Shults Dot Com has created this privacy statement in order to
demonstrate our firm commitment to privacy.
The following discloses our
information gathering and dissemination practices for this website: Shults Dot Com.We use your IP address to help diagnose problems with our server,
and to administer our Web site.
Your IP address is used to help identify you and your shopping cart.Our site uses cookies to keep track of your shopping cart and to make sure you don't see the same ad repeatedly.
We use cookies to deliver content specific to your interests and to save your password so you don't have to re-enter it each time you visit our site.Our site's registration form requires users to give us contact information (like their name and email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
We use customer contact information from the registration form to send the user information about our company.
The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and to bill the user for products and services.
Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor the visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
** MAKE SURE that you explain the other data that you mentioned you collect here. **This site contains links to other sites.
Shults Dot Com is not responsible for the privacy practices or the content of such Web sites.(*Since you indicated that there are special relationships, such as "Powered by" partners, business partners, cobranded sites, then these relationships must be addressed in your privacy statement.
These relationships need to be clearly defined and it must be clear who is receiving the information collected by the site and who has access to this information.
It must be clear what type of information is shared.
Is only select information shared?
Is the sharing of information limited to only aggregate information?)Our site uses an order form for customers to request information, products, and services.
We collect visitor's contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
Contact information from the order form is used to send orders, information about our company, and promotional material from some of our partners to our customers.
The customer's contact information is also used to get in touch with the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.
Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
** MAKE SURE that you explain the other data that you mentioned you collect here. **Our online surveys ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
We use contact data from our surveys to send the user information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.
The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected from our users is used to check the users' qualifications and bill the user for products and services.
Unique identifiers (such as social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
** MAKE SURE that you explain the other data that you mentioned you collect here. **We run contests on our site in which we ask visitors for contact information (like their email address), unique identifiers (like their social security number), financial information (like their account or credit card numbers), and demographic information (like their zip code, age, or income level).
We use contact data from our contests to send users information about our company and promotional material from some of our partners.
The customer's contact information is also used to contact the visitor when necessary.
Users may opt-out of receiving future mailings; see the choice/opt-out section below.
Financial information that is collected from our users is used to check the users' qualifications for registration and bill the user for products and services.
Unique identifiers (like social security numbers) are collected from Web site visitors to verify the user's identity and for use as account numbers in our record system.
Demographic and profile data is also collected at our site.
We use this data to tailor our visitor's experience at our site, showing them content that we think they might be interested in, and displaying the content according to their preferences.
** MAKE SURE that you explain the other data that you mentioned you collect here. **** DON'T FORGET to include a description of the other services
that you have that collect information here.Public Forums
This site makes chat rooms, forums, message boards, and/or news groups available to its users.
Please remember that any information that is disclosed in these areas becomes public information and you should exercise caution when deciding to disclose your personal information.Security
This site has security measures in place to protect the loss, misuse and alteration of the information under our control. (*Please elaborate on the security measures that you have in place.)Children's Guidelines
According to the answers that you have chosen, your Web site meets the guidelines of TRUSTe's Children's program.NOT collect online contact information without prior parental consent or parental notification, which will include an opportunity for the parent to prevent use of the information and participation in the activity.
Without prior parental consent, online information will only be used to respond directly to the child's request and will not be used for other purposes without prior parental consentNOT collect personally identifiable offline contact information without prior parental consentNOT distribute to third parties any personally identifiable information with out prior parental consentNOT give the ability to publicly post or otherwise distribute personally identifiable contact information without prior parental consentNOT entice by the prospect of a special game, prize or other activity, to divulge more information than is needed to participate in the activityChoice/Opt-OutOur site provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from us and our partners at the point where we request information about the visitor.This site gives users the following options for removing their information from our database to not receive future communications or to no longer receive our service.
You can send email to support@shults.comYou can send mail to the following postal address:
23864 Sycamore Dr., Mission Viejo, CA 92691
You can call the following telephone number: 949-768-2609You can many tools allow the use to choose optionsCorrect/Update
This site gives users the following options for changing and modifying
information previously provided.
email support@shults.comsend mail to the following postal address:
23864 Sycamore Dr., Mission Viejo, CA 92691
call the following telephone number: 949-768-2609Contacting the Web Site
If you have any questions about this privacy statement, the
practices of this site, or your dealings with this Web site,
Copyright © 1996-2007 Shults Dot Com. All rights reserved. Comments and questions: Send email to
Privacy Policy
